# NATALIA ANDREOLA

# FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

E: nathy.andreola@gmail.com | P: 647-338-9720 | nataliaandreola.com

# PROFILE

I am a Front-End Web Developer with business and marketing experience. My technical skillset combined with my experience working with developers, supporting clients and website management, pushes me to build applications that put users' needs at the core.

With a strong collaborative mindset, I value knowledge sharing, and bringing new ideas to keep the team moving in the right direction.

## SKILLS

- HTML5
- JavaScript
- CSS3
- SASS
- React¡Query
- Firebase
- GitHub
- PSD Conversion
- Responsive Design
- Web Accessibility Requirements
- Team Collaboration

# FEATURED PROJECT

### **GroceryFy App**

Built using React and Firebase

It is a shopping list where users can add/remove items from the list https://nataliaandreolaproject5.firebaseapp.com/

# EDUCATION

# Web Development Immersive Certificate

Sep 2019

Juno College of Technology (Formerly HackerYou) | Toronto

#### **Diploma in Business Marketing**

2011 - 2012

Centennial College | Toronto

#### **Bachelor in Business Admin**

2005 - 2008

Cruzeiro do Sul University | Sao Paulo, Brazil

# EXPERIENCE

#### Bus. Development Asst. / Bookkeeper | BGD LLP, Mississauga

2015 - 2019

- Managed reports to ensure deadlines were being met and engagements were following at an achievable time, especially during the busy tax season
- Promoted to bookkeeper where effectively managed 20+ clients' payroll and bookkeeping using Sage 50, requiring attention to detail and accuracy

### Social Media Manager | 2vLive, Toronto

2013 - 2014

 Successfully managed day-to-day content on social media platforms, which resulted in a 100% increase in the number of followers

#### Marketing Coordinator | Stellar Point, Whitby

2013 - 2013

 Monitored the website and worked with the developers team to ensure all information was up-to-date and accurate



